{
    "subject": "resource/List_of_Modern_Family_characters",
    "predicate": "ontology/portrayer",
    "object": "resource/Sarah_Hyland",
    "human_readable": "Sarah Hyland portrays characters on Modern Family.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.848843514919281,
            "question": "Who plays characters on Modern Family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7202516794204712,
            "question": "Does Sarah Hyland appear in any other TV shows besides Modern Family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6897842884063721,
            "question": "What kind of roles does Sarah Hyland play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6473036408424377,
            "question": "Who are some other actors on Modern Family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6046889424324036,
            "question": "Name a show featuring Sarah Hyland."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5684800744056702,
            "question": "What is Sarah Hyland known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5098768472671509,
            "question": "Is Sarah Hyland an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39792880415916443,
            "question": "Is Modern Family a comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34864169359207153,
            "question": "What is the name of the popular sitcom starring Sarah Hyland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3332591950893402,
            "question": "What TV show does Sarah Hyland appear in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sarah Hyland portrays characters on Modern Family.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8325_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the popular sitcom starring Sarah Hyland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8325_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Modern Family a comedy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8325_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sarah Hyland an actress?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8325_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8325_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Sarah Hyland portrays characters on Modern Family\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents mention that Sarah Hyland plays a character (Haley Dunphy) in the TV show \"Modern Family\", indicating that she indeed portrays characters on the show."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information supporting that Sarah Hyland has portrayed characters on the show \"Modern Family,\" including roles such as Haley Dunphy and her recent guest appearance."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}